I expected Zionist to be upset, but I definitely didn't expect this level.
I'm getting the royal Zionist treatment right now.
They are dragging me through all corners of the internet, but it's okay.
I can take it.
Did you flee because you guys are killing too many babies?
Were you guys in the I.O.F.?
IDF.
You were in the I.O.F.?
How many babies did you kill?
How many women did you rape?
You didn't kill babies?
How many children did you rape?
We've seen it. You record it. You put it on your fucking kin.
Do you listen to what they say?
Across my country. Really proud.
You're proud to be a fucking sociopathic.
Everyone's talking about it. The entire world's fucking talking about it.
You're worse than that, actually.
You're telling the people that we drew the holocaust.
You didn't go through the holocaust.
You're creating a holocaust.
You guys are doing the holocaust.
You guys are doing a holocaust right now.
Yeah.
You created a holocaust.
Slaughtering Palestinians.
Free Palestine.
Free Palestinian motherfuckers.
Oh my god.
Ew.
Why are we all the same?
That's crazy.
After coming off of a baby killing spree, they get to just come to New York City and fucking chill.
I don't think that anyone, like, brought them into secondary screening, like, coming into the United States of America.
America.
Oh, Jesus.
Fuck Israel!
This is a testament to the fact that you guys are losing.
Yes, I said what I said and I would say it again.
And that's the thing, right?
You didn't say I was wrong.
You just said I was anti-Semitic.
You can take my job.
You can take my professional reputation.
You can take my license.
You can threaten me with anything under the sun.
It still will not change the truth.
And the truth is, the entire world has seen your crimes, your lies, your arrogance, your sadism, your complete disdain for anyone who is not like you or anyone who does not submit to you.
You guys breathe genocidal.
It is clear to everyone, yourselves probably included, that you have forever lost.
There is no amount of PR or paid influencers or free trips to the rape apartheid colony that can change the public opinion on Zionism and Israel.
Yesterday, Israel launched a genocidal assault on Lebanon, killing at least 210 people.
And you guys are still trying to convince the world that your hurt feelings over the fucking truth are worse than the actual truth?
If you can't handle the truth, then maybe it's time to change your ways.
Is that anti-Semitic too?
Hi, Guala Zy.
Guala Zy.